{
  "d": {
    "results": [
      {
        "__metadata": {
          "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/AnsQuesSectionSet('1')",
          "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/AnsQuesSectionSet('1')",
          "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.AnsQuesSection"
        },
        "Q2section": "1",
        "Q2refid": "6000003629",
        "NavAnsQues": {
          "results": [
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q30')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q30')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "02",
              "Qid": "Q30",
              "Question": "IS YOUR COMPANY REGISTERED IN ANY NATIONAL LEVL STOCK MARKET ?",
              "Answer": "No"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "10",
              "Qid": "Q40",
              "Question": "SELECT COUNTRY",
              "Answer": "AUSTRIA"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "10",
              "Qid": "Q40",
              "Question": "DOSE THE REVENUES FOR ONE OF THE SHAREHOLDERS OR THE PARENT COMPANY EXCEEDED $ 70 MILLION SAUDIS OR EQUIVALENT DURING THE 2015 OR 2016?",
              "Answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "10",
              "Qid": "Q40",
              "Question": "Dose THE ASSETS FOR ONE OF THE SHAREHOLDERS OR THE PARENT COMPANY EXCEEDED $ 100 MILLION SAUDIS OR EQUIVALENT DURING THE 2015 OR 2016?",
              "Answer": "No"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "10",
              "Qid": "Q40",
              "Question": "DOSE THE NET PROFIT FOR ONE OF THE SHAREHOLDERS OR THE PARENT COMPANY EXCEEDED $ 50 MILLION SAUDIS OR EQUIVALENT DURING THE 2015 OR 2016?",
              "Answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "10",
              "Qid": "Q40",
              "Question": "DOES THE ENTITY REQUIRED LICENSE OR ONE OF THE SHAREHOLDERS 3 REGIONAL BRANCHES OUTSIDE OF THEIR COUNTRY?",
              "Answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "10",
              "Qid": "Q40",
              "Question": "IS THE PERCENT OF ENTITY EXPORT PRODUCTS IN THE HOME COUNTRY 50% OR MORE?",
              "Answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "10",
              "Qid": "Q40",
              "Question": "IS THE SIZE OF THE WORKFORCE OF THE ENTITY 10 THOUSAND PERSON OR MORE?",
              "Answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q40')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "10",
              "Qid": "Q40",
              "Question": "DOES THE ENTITY REQUIRED LICENSE OR ONE OF THE SHAREHOLDERS PATENTED RELATING TO THE ACTIVITY TO BE LICENSED?",
              "Answer": "Yes"
            }
          ]
        }
      },
      {
        "__metadata": {
          "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/AnsQuesSectionSet('2')",
          "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/AnsQuesSectionSet('2')",
          "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.AnsQuesSection"
        },
        "Q2section": "2",
        "Q2refid": "6000003629",
        "NavAnsQues": {
          "results": [
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q10')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('Q10')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "1",
              "Qid": "Q10",
              "Question": "LICENSE TYPE",
              "Answer": "INDUSTRIAL  صناعي"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('IQ1')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('IQ1')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "B",
              "Qid": "IQ1",
              "Question": "ISIC Section",
              "Answer": "Mining and quarrying"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('IQ2')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('IQ2')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "22",
              "Qid": "IQ2",
              "Question": "ISIC Division",
              "Answer": "Manufacture of rubber and plastics products"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('IQ4')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('IQ4')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "5",
              "Qid": "IQ4",
              "Question": "Complimentary",
              "Answer": " اتاحة امكانية ادراج البند الجمركي وكمية المنتج من قبل العميل"
            },
            {
              "__metadata": {
                "id": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('IQ5')",
                "uri": "https://sagngdap03.hec.sagia.gov.sa:44300/sap/opu/odata/sap/ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV/answeredquestiondisplaySet('IQ5')",
                "type": "ZQEEMAH2_EXT_SRV.answeredquestiondisplay"
              },
              "Answerkey": "15",
              "Qid": "IQ5",
              "Question": "Activity Description",
              "Answer": " يلزم المنشاءة الحصول على الترخيص الصناعي النهائي من وزارة الطاقة والصناعة والثروة المعدنية"
            }
          ]
        }
      }
    ]
  }
}